Guide to the Friendship House Association records, 1904-1992 MS2142
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administration, 1910-1991; MS2142 Series 2; 18.5 Linear feet (Box 37, Box 38, Box 29, Box 31, Box 32, Box 30, Box 34, Box 33, Box 36, Box 35, Box 23, Box 22, Box 25, Box 24, Box 27, Box 26, Box 20, Box 28, Box 21, Box 16, Box 15, Box 18, Box 17, Box 12, Box 11, Box 14, Box 13, Box 8, Box 7, Box 10
  - House Committee n.d., undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - House Committee, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - House Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - House Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - House Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - House Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - House Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - House Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - House Committee, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Legislative and Governmental Affairs Committee, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Legislative and Governmental Affairs Committee, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Legislative and Governmental Affairs Committee, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Legislative and Governmental Affairs Committee, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Membership Committee, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Membership Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Membership Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Membership Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Membership Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Membership Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Membership Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Administration, undated (Box 26)
  - Membership Committee, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Membership Committee, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Membership Committee, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Membership Committee, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Membership Committee, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Membership Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Membership Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Membership Committee, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Membership Committee, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Membership Committee, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Membership Committee, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Membership Committee, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - .Membership Committee, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Membership Committee, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Membership Committee, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - .Membership Committee, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Membership Committee, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Membership Committee, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Membership Committee, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Membership Committee, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Nominating Committee, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Nominating Committee, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Nominating Committee, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Nominating Committee, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Nominating Committee, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Nominating Committee, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Nominating Committee, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Nominating Committee, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Nominating Committee, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Nominating Committee, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Nominating Committee, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Nominating Committee, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Nominating Committee, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Nominating Committee, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Personnel Committee, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Personnel Committee, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Personnel Committee, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Personnel Committee, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Personnel Committee, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Personnel Committee, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Personnel Committee, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Personnel Committee, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Personnel Committee, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Personnel Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Personnel Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Personnel Committee, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Personnel Committee, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Personnel Committee, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Personnel Committee, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Personnel Committee, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Personnel Committee, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Personnel Committee, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Personnel Committee, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Administration, undated (Box 27)
  - Planning Committee, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Planning Committee, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Planning Committee, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Planning Committee, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Planning Committee, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Planning Committee, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Planning Committee, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Planning Committee, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Planning Committee, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Planning Committee, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Planning Committee, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Planning Committee, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Planning Committee, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Planning Committee, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Planning Committee, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Program Committee, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Program Committee, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Program Committee, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Program Committee, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Program Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Program Committee, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Program Committee, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Program Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Program Committee, 1959-1962 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Program Committee, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Program Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Program Committee, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Program Committee, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Program Committee, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Program Committee, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Program Committee, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Program Committee, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Program Committee, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Program Committee, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Program Committee, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Program Planning and Development Committee, n.d., undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Program Planning and Development Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Program Planning and Development Committee, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Program Planning and Development Committee, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Program Planning and Development Committee, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Program Planning and Development Committee, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Administration, undated (Box 28)
  - Public Welfare Committee, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Public Welfare Committee, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Public Welfare Committee, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Public Welfare Committee, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Public Welfare Committee, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Public Welfare Committee, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Public Welfare Committee, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Volunteer Committee, n.d., undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Volunteer Committee, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Volunteer Committee, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Volunteer Committee, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Volunteer Committee, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Volunteer Committee, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Volunteer Committee, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Volunteer Committee, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1968, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Administration, undated (Box 29)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1920 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1920 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1927 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence of Henry P. Blair and General Correspondence, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - General correspondence, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - General correspondence, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - General correspondence, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - General correspondence, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Staff salaries, purchase of "The Maples", 1935-1937 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Staff salaries, purchase of "The Maples", 1935-1937 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - General correspondence, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - General correspondence, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - General correspondence, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - General correspondence, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - General correspondence, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - General correspondence, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - General correspondence, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - General correspondence, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - General correspondence, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - General correspondence, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - General correspondence, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - General correspondence, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Administration, undated (Box 30)
  - Staff lists, correspondence, director's report, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Staff lists, correspondence, director's report, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Staff lists, correspondence, director's report, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Staff lists, correspondence, director's report, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Staff lists, correspondence, director's report, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Staff lists, correspondence, director's report, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Staff lists, correspondence, director's report, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, staff lists, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, staff lists, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, staff lists, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Hospitalization plan, other administrative matters, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Hospitalization plan, other administrative matters, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Maintenance, 1947-1949 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, staff notes, accident reports, press releases, maintenance -, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, staff notes, accident reports, press releases, maintenance -, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, staff notes, accident reports, press releases, maintenance -, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, staff notes, accident reports, press releases, maintenance -, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, staff notes, accident reports, press releases, maintenance -, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, staff notes, accident reports, press releases, maintenance -, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, staff notes, accident reports, press releases, maintenance -, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, staff notes, accident reports, press releases, maintenance -, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, insurance -, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, insurance -, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence of Director John Guinessy, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Administration, undated (Box 31)
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Junior Recreation study, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Junior Recreation study, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Junior Recreation study, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Junior Recreation study, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Retirement manual, press releases, insurance, 1960 ca. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Retirement manual, press releases, insurance, 1960 ca. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Retirement manual, press releases, insurance, 1960 ca. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Retirement manual, press releases, insurance, 1960 ca. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Retirement manual, press releases, insurance, 1960 ca. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence of Reinhart B. Gutman, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Policies, 1960 ca. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Staff meetings, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Gutman correspondence, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Articles on Mr. Gutman, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Articles on Mr. Gutman, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Staff salaries, benefits, policies for dismissal, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Staff salaries, benefits, policies for dismissal, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Staff salaries, benefits, policies for dismissal, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - General correspondence by months, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - General correspondence by months, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - President Hans Klagsbrunn correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - President Hans Klagsbrunn correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Staff meetings, public relations, maintenance, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Staff meetings, public relations, maintenance, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Staff meetings, public relations, maintenance, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - General correspondence by month, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - General correspondence by month, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - General correspondence by month, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - General correspondence by month, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - General correspondence by month, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Administration, undated (Box 32)
  - Staff meetings, personnel code, correspondence, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Staff meetings, personnel code, correspondence, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Staff meetings, personnel code, correspondence, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence by month, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - General correspondence by month, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - General correspondence by month, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence on Urban Center Proposal, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Welcome to Robert T. Adams, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Articles on Robert T. Adams, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Articles on Robert T. Adams, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Job openings, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Organizational outline of Friendship House, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Personnel code, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - VIP visits to Friendship House, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - VIP visits to Friendship House, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Staff and staff roster, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Director's report and projections, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - General correspondence, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Personnel code, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - About a new day care director, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - About a group work supervisor and volunteer coordinator, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Press releases and visitors, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Press releases and visitors, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Washington Post reporter's visit to Friendship House, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Testimony on DC appropriations, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - General correspondence, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Leases on clothing center, antipoverty offices, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Executive Director's annual report to Board, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Article, photos of Robert T. Adams 196., undated (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Article, photos of Robert T. Adams 196., undated (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Salaries, personnel, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Salaries, personnel, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Lady Bird Johnson's visit, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Announcement of programs, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Press releases, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Employment controversy and picketing, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Memos, plans, correspondence, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Memos, plans, correspondence, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Memos, plans, correspondence, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Memos, plans, correspondence, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Memos, plans, correspondence, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Protest on hiring practices, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Press releases, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Administration, undated (Box 33)
  - Public relations, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Public relations, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Staff roster, meetings, notices -, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Staff roster, meetings, notices -, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Staff roster, meetings, notices -, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Staff roster, meetings, notices -, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Insurance, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Memos, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Job descriptions, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Supervisor's reports, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Staff group work reports, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - "What's Going On" memos, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Executive Director's testimony, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Personnel notes, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Press releases, publicity -, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Press releases, publicity -, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Press releases, publicity -, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Press releases, publicity --McCalls Magazine notice -Japanese cabinet members' wives visit, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors Klagsbrunn dinner, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Director's memos, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Director's memos, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Director's memos, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Staff meetings, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Folders Moved, undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Folders Moved, undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - General correspondence, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Director's reports, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Director's reports, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Director's reports, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Employee, staff files, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Maintenance, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Memos "What's Going On", 1968 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Public relations, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Public relations, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 37)